新奥尔良  凌晨3点
欢迎你们  年轻的创业者
Welcome, my young entrepreneurs.
人们说生活没有捷径
They say there are no shortcuts in life.
人们说没有免费的午餐
They say nothing is free.
但我现在告诉你们  我要跟你们做的交易
But I'm telling you right now, the deal I'm going to give you
是你们所能得的最接近免费的机会
is the closest thing to free you'll ever get.
你们都听说了传闻  不然也不会来这里
You all heard the rumors. Otherwise, you wouldn't be here.
现在你们有机会亲眼得见了
Now's your chance to see it up close.
我免费提供产品给你们
I give you the product for free.
你们将其卖掉
You sell it.
这么好的事听起来不像真的
Sounds too good to be true.
但确实是真的
That's because it is.
我们不会在新奥尔良停留太久
We'll only be in New Orleans for a little while,
所以赶紧拿去卖吧
so get out there and sell.
这东西叫什么
What's it called?
你的问题还真多
You ask a lot of questions.
没错  我叫纽特
Yeah, I'm Newt.
纽特
Newt.
这个
This...
是超能药
is Power.
超能计划
奥尔良县报警电话
Orleans Parish, 9-1-1.
我朋友现在的反应很奇怪
My friend is having some strange reaction right now.
她吃了一颗药
She just took a pill.
我告诉你  老兄
This is what I'm telling you, man,
他把那辆车举过了头顶
he lifted the freaking car over his head.
报警电话  您有什么紧急情况
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
我不知道该怎么形容
I don't know how to describe this,
但我刚刚看到了怪事
but I just seen some weird shit.
我完全没看到血  没流一滴血
Look, I don't see no blood at all. No blood.
报警电话  您报警的情况在哪里
9-1-1, where is your emergency?
六周后
报警电话
Nine-one-one.
♪ 超能  超能 ♪
♪ Power, power ♪
♪ 说话高点音量 ♪
♪ Speak a little louder ♪
♪ 若你有空听  我能唱上几小时 ♪
♪ If you got the time, I bet you I could spit for hours ♪
♪ 这个世界满是淤泥 ♪
♪ Will be something so ugly ♪
♪ 但我出淤泥而不染 ♪
♪ But I'm pretty as a flower ♪
♪ 对金钱耽耽虎视 ♪
♪ Hungry for that money ♪
♪ 我要将其吞噬 ♪
♪ I'm coming to devour ♪
♪ 妙语连珠  源源不绝 ♪
♪ Shower, dropping heavy bars up off a tower ♪
♪ 这是我的拿手好戏  大家都叫我球场之王 ♪
♪ Know I got that game, my people call me Dwight Howard ♪
♪ 我就是那个黑人小孩  不怯懦的勇者 ♪
♪ I'm that kid, this Black kid, no cowards ♪
♪ 唱出抱负让世人明了 ♪
♪ Spit it so they get it ♪
♪ 我浑身充满超能 ♪
♪ I'm embedded with the power ♪
小鸟
Bird!
Robin有知更鸟之意
小鸟
Bird!
算了  老兄  这里没有小鸟
Come on, man. There's no bird.
我们根本不该这个时候来这里
We shouldn't even be here right now.
小鸟
Bird!
-快出来  小鸟  -你没听我说话吗
- Come on, bird! - You're not even listening.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
兄弟  把手举起来
Say, bro, let me see your hands.
举起手来  快点
Hands, now!
你没有枪
You don't got no gun.
不信就试试
You wanna find out?
多少钱
How much?
五百
Five hundred.
五百  你认真的吗
Five hundred? Are you serious?
市场供求决定的  到底要不要
Supply and demand. You want it or not?
我想爽一把
I wanna climb the walls.
这东西不是那种功效
That's not how it works.
你吃下去  药效五分钟  效果因人而异
You take it, for five minutes, you get what you get.
别收钱了  不如直接给我们
Instead of selling it to us, why don't you just give it to us?
-别碰我  放手  -把她的面罩摘了
- Don't touch me! Get off! - Take that stupid mask off!
不
No!
放开我  放手
Leave me alone! Get off!
放开我  把包还给我
Get off me! Give me my bag!
把我的包还给我
Give me my bag!
-别动  她包里有多少  -就三颗
- Stop! How many has she got? - Just three.
不过我打赌她还有货
But I bet this chick has more.
先生们  跪下双手抱头
Gentlemen, on your knees, hands behind your head.
新奥尔良警局
NOPD.
这还有位女士呢  你也一样跪下抱头
I see we have a lady here, as well. You too, ma'am.
抱头  好的  谢谢
Hands, very good. Thank you.
大家今晚过得还愉快吗
Now, how's everybody doing tonight?
你确定想那么做吗  小伙子
You sure you want to do that, young man?
你以前吃过那东西吗
You ever taken one of those before?
没吃过对吧  我看得出来
You haven't, have you? I can tell.
我猜你听说这东西能让你行动迅速力大无比
Now, I bet you've heard it can make you fast, make you strong.
即便我拿枪指着你
Make this a fair fight,
我们也算势均力敌
even though I got a gun pointed at your face.
汤米  扭一下
Just twist it, Tommy.
不过前提是你恰巧拿到一颗好的超能药
But that's only if you happen to have a good Power.
并非所有人有此好运
Not everybody does.
有些人吃了就直接自爆了
Some people take it and just blow up.
-我不想再玩了  兄弟  -闭嘴
- I don't wanna do this anymore, man. - Shut up.
那么问题来了  你会有怎样的超能
So the question is, what's your power?
结果是好是坏  没人知道
Might be good, might be bad, nobody knows.
把药吞了  汤米
Take the pill, Tommy.
吞吧
Take it.
吞下去
Go ahead.
我想看看会发生什么
I wanna see what happens.
你们走运了  我只有一副手铐
You boys are lucky I only have one pair of cuffs.
不然就把你们都拘了
I'd bring you all in.
你们走吧
You can go now.
走啊
Go!
老兄  你真疯
Man, you crazy.
你还好吗
You okay?
我能搞定
I had it.
我看到的可不是那样
That is not what I saw.
怎么  你对着镜子练习过吗
So what, you practice that in the mirror?
你肯定练习过
Yeah, you did.
我打赌你练习的时候也拔枪了
I bet you had your gun out too.
拿枪指着镜子里的自己
Pointed at yourself,
模仿克林特·伊斯特伍德那样讲狠话
talking all hard like you Clint Eastwood.
你才不了解我
You don't know me.
我了解
Yeah, I do.
你对克林特·伊斯特伍德有什么了解
What do you know about Clint Eastwood?
我知道的挺多
I know enough.
你看过他哪些片子
What you seen him in?
《廊桥遗梦》
The Bridges of Madison County.
那部电影很不错
That's actually a pretty good one.
对了  你兜里那颗药要五百块
By the way, it's 500 for that pill in your pocket.
和上次一样的东西吗
The same stuff as last time?
-是啊  不然还能是啥  -我哪知道
- Yeah, what else it gonna be? - I don't know.
是从上次那家伙那里拿的货吗
Did you get it from the same guy as last time?
得了  你不能既当警察又当顾客
Come on, you either gonna be a cop or a customer.
没那么简单
It's not that simple.
罪犯用这东西
Bad guys using this stuff
一个人就能干掉整个分局的警察
to take out whole precincts of cops single-handed.
我只是想双方公平竞争
I'm just trying to level the playing field.
小心服用
Be careful with that.
谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
-你觉得这摩托车怎么样  -还行
- What do you think of the bike? - It's an all right bike.
那你想不想要
Well, you want it or not?
-我开来送你的  -你骗人
- I mean, I brought it here for you. - You lying.
我没有  之前你不是过生日吗
No, you said it was your birthday the other day, right?
-那都一个月前了  -好吧  那算了
- That was a month ago. - Okay then, you know what? Never mind.
-不  我想要这摩托车  -确定吗
- No, I mean, I want the bike. - Yeah, you sure?
是的
Yeah.
车座上怎么缠满了胶带
Why the seat made out of duct tape?
这是扣押车场里最好的一辆了
It was nicest one at the impound lot.
-给我了吗  -骑上去吧
- It's mine? - Get on!
我靠
Damn!
爸爸的乖女儿
早安  新奥尔良
Good morning, New Orleans!
有听众来电  告诉我你看到了什么
I have a caller on the line. Tell me exactly what you saw.
我昨晚看见一个小孩在珀依德拉斯路上跑
Man, I saw a kid running down Poydras last night,
时速有55公里
35 miles per hour.
你难道用测速枪测了那孩子吗
Did you have a speed gun on this guy?
如果街道限速是40  他不费吹灰之力就超了
Man, if the speed limit is 25, he passed it down cold.
我敢肯定  他一定嗑药了
I'm telling you, he was on something.
老兄  听起来磕了药的大概是你吧
Bruh, it sounds like you might have been on something.
维恩  随便你怎么拿我打趣
Wayne, you can make fun all you want,
但我敢肯定  这里面有问题
but I'm telling you, something going on.
有视频为证  我前几天看到
There's videos. I saw one the other day,
一个孩子从赌场楼顶跳下来
a kid jumped straight off the roof of the casino
毫发无损
and just walked away.
也许有什么阴谋在酝酿...
Maybe there's a little conspiracy going...
纽特
迪高公寓
谁啊
Who is it?
我找纽特
Looking for Newt.
我没问你找谁  我问你是谁
I ain't ask who you're looking for, I said, "Who is it?"
先生我明白  我是赛蒙的朋友
I understand that, sir. I'm a friend of Simon's.
从坦帕来的
I'm from Tampa.
他让我来找你  也许你想做点生意
He sent me here to talk to you. Maybe you wanna do some business.
走到我能看见你的地方
Come where I can see you.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
你一个人吗
You alone?
我们都是孤身一人
Aren't we all?
把手举起来
Let me see your hands.
我手里拿着箱子
I got a box in my hands.
你想让我举手还是让我把箱子放下
You wanna see my hands, or put the box down?
-怎样  -是的
- What you want? - Yeah...
-不  -怎样  放下箱子  举起手
- No. - Which one? Box down, hands up?
把箱子放下然后把手举起来
Put the box down and get your hands up.
-好的  我放下箱子  -对
- Okay, I'm with you. Box down. - Yeah, just...
-慢点  慢慢地  -好的  我慢慢地
- Now, slow, real slow now. - Yeah, slow, everything's slow.
如果你想  可以打电话给赛蒙  证实我的身份
If you want, you can call Simon. He'll verify who I am.
跟他说少校来找你了
Tell him that the Major's here to see you.
少校
The Major.
这样  兄弟
Say, bruh.
我去打电话  你站这里别动
I'ma go make that call. You stay right there.
别那么做
I wouldn't do that.
纽特
Newt.
我不想伤害你
I don't wanna hurt you.
我不想伤害任何人
I don't wanna hurt nobody.
我只是需要一些信息而已
Just need some information, that's all.
告诉我你这东西哪里来的  我马上就走
Tell me where you're getting this stuff, and I'll get out of here.
你不愿意聊聊吗
You don't wanna talk?
你只需要告诉我是谁给你供货的
All you gotta do is tell me who your supplier is.
怎么样  纽特  我们能谈谈吗
So what you think about that, Newt, huh? We got a deal?
只要告诉我
Once I get that information,
你就能缩回
you can slither back to whatever hole
你藏身的窝里去了  明白吗
that you came out of, understand?
听听我的声音
Listen to my voice.
我在说谎吗
Am I lying?
什么情况  你不...
What? I know you not...
滚出我的厨房
Get the hell out of my kitchen!
老天
Oh, Lord!
纽特  你会害死这里的人的
Newt, you gonna get somebody killed in here!
你从哪里弄来的这玩意
Where you getting this shit from?
是谁制造的  告诉我供货源是哪里
Who's making it? Tell me the source!
我什么都不会告诉你的
I ain't telling you shit!
马上告诉我  是谁给你供的货
Tell me right now! Who's the supplier?
告诉我名字
Give me one name!
快告诉我
You gonna tell me!
告诉我是谁
Tell me who it is!
好吧  是大佬
Okay. Big Man.
-他叫大佬  -快说  小子
- His name's Biggie. - Speak up, son!
我只知道这么多
That's all I know, man!
他在哪
Where's he at? I...
大佬在哪
Where's Biggie?
你吃了多少
How many did you take?
不  爸爸  爸爸
No! Daddy! Daddy!
先生  醒醒
Hey, mister.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
他还活着
He's alive, man.
罗宾
Robin.
你起了吗
Are you up?
-罗宾  -嗯
- Robin. - Yeah.
你迟到了
You late.
我这就起
I'm up.
妈  你还好吗
Ma, you okay?
我挺好的  宝贝  马上就出来
Yeah, baby. Be right out.
我给你煮点汤
I'll make you some soup.
老天  我们断粮了
Man, we all out.
直接去学校
Just get to school.
我回头再买点
I'm go pick some up later.
还有你的药
And your prescription too.
初步调查指出这可能是个自制冰毒的窝点
The initial investigation is indicating a home meth lab,
伍德梅尔致命火灾
但我们要等看过完整调查报告
but we're gonna wait until we see the full report
-才能下定论  -嗯
- before we make an assessment. - Yeah.
该建筑数年前就被判定为危楼
It was deemed unsafe years ago.
纽特不是在那边混吗
Isn't that where Newt hangs out?
我不确定  可能是
I'm not sure, could be.
替我给你表哥发个短信  宝贝
Text your cousin for me, baby.
这火还挺大的
That's a pretty big fire.
他肯定没事  妈
I'm sure he's fine, Ma.
从一到十级  你今天有多不舒服
On a scale of one to ten, how bad is it today?
七  七级半
Seven, seven and a half.
抱歉  妈
I'm sorry, Ma.
你得走了
You gotta go.
我今晚会给你
Well, I'll come through
买药和汤回来的
with your prescription and your soup tonight.
我的英雄
My hero.
想来点配乐吗
Want some company?
好了
All right, then.
表哥  你还好吗
你住的地方好像爆炸了
胎儿酒精综合症是一种
This is a major problem during pregnancy
孕期常见问题
known as FAS.
我没事  跑出来了  得低调一点
是孕期摄入酒精以及服用毒品
Birth defects caused by drinking alcohol
导致的先天缺陷
and using drugs while pregnant.
我们应当如何预防这种先天缺陷
How do we prevent these birth defects?
-收起来  -女士们
- Put that up. - Ladies.
我猜你们在讨论胎儿在子宫中
I'm guessing that you're discussing what the condition is called
受到酒精影响导致的疾病名称  是不是
when a child is exposed to alcohol in the womb, right?
虚弱酒精综合征
F... feeble alcohol syndrome.
胎儿
Fetal.
但是正确
But yes, correct.
现在我们来谈谈预防方法
Now, let's talk about prevention.
我们应当如何预防这种先天缺陷
How do we prevent these birth defects?
拒绝酒精毒品
No drugs, no alcohol.
还在我手上
能见个面吗
什么时候
老时间
很简单  只有胎儿酒精综合征...
Simple. It is the only form known as FAS...
我知道你觉得这些知识不重要
I know that you don't think this stuff is serious,
你觉得无所谓  但它确实很重要
you don't think it's important, but it is.
罗宾  你这门课要挂科了
Right now, you're getting a D in this class, Robin.
这是门简单的课
It's an easy class.
安静
Quiet.
既然你不在乎你的成绩
So since you don't seem to be worried
或者能不能毕业
about your grades or graduating...
你肯定有别的计划  对吧
you must have a plan, right?
是什么计划呢  莱利小姐
So what is that plan, Miss Reilly?
说唱
Rap.
她要当说唱歌手
She'll rap.
我懂了
I see.
那你起来给我们唱一段吧
Well, then, why don't you get up and rap for us?
让我相信你确实能行
Make me believe that you've got a shot,
那我今年就让你及格
and I'll give you a C for the year.
♪ 老师和学生究竟有什么区别 ♪
♪ Now what's the difference between a student and a teacher ♪
♪ 一个会长大  一个会老去 ♪
♪ While one of them is growing up, the other's getting weaker ♪
♪ 因此你就要当个变态吗 ♪
♪ Is the criteria for you to be a creeper ♪
♪ 走廊里鬼鬼祟祟  鞋子吱嘎作响 ♪
♪ Stalking the halls in squeaky little shoes ♪
♪ 买双球鞋好吗 ♪
♪ Get you some sneakers ♪
♪ 买新鞋  机灵点  看眼色 ♪
♪ Get new kicks, get a clue, get a hint ♪
♪ 交朋友  过生活 ♪
♪ Get a friend, get a life ♪
♪ 娶老婆  赚大钱 ♪
♪ Get a wife, get a mint ♪
♪ 你的黄牙总露出来  赶紧去做个漂白 ♪
♪ And your teeth been looking yellow, get an off-white tint ♪
♪ 从未当过优等  但我气运如虹 ♪
♪ Never honor roll but I'm on a roll like lint ♪
♪ 我知道我正把你嘲弄 ♪
♪ Yeah, I see I'm digging at your pride ♪
♪ 你以为你能隐瞒  这体制就是个谎言 ♪
♪ You thought that you could hide that the system is a lie ♪
♪ 根本不是为我而建 ♪
♪ Wasn't built for me to thrive ♪
♪ 专门打压我这样的人 ♪
♪ It don't love nobody like me ♪
♪ 文凭不能定义我的现在和将来 ♪
♪ Diplomas won't determine who I am or who I might be ♪
♪ 下次你还想拿我当笑料 ♪
♪ So next time you tempted to pick on me for a laugh ♪
♪ 别整这些虚的  有话直说 ♪
♪ Skip theatrics and just tell me ♪
♪ 我才不上你的课  贱人 ♪
♪ I can get up out your class, bitch ♪
好啊  这才对
Yeah! That's my girl.
坐下  打住
Sit down! Stop!
-罗宾  -坐下
- Robin! - Sit down.
- Robin! - Sit down!
-把她放下来  -罗宾
- Put her down! - Robin!
那好
Well, then.
要么你把手机给我
You can give me that phone
要么你去办公室
or you can go to the office.
我们再说回预防方法
Let's get back to prevention, please.
没有一劳永逸的神奇药丸
There is no magic pill to fix it.
市中心储蓄银行附近发生武装抢劫
Reports of armed robbery downtown near the Savings bank.
请所有待命警员出警
All available officers please respond.
先生  你在里面看到了什么
Sir, what'd you see in there?
我不知道  我没看到他
I don't know, I didn't see him.
他是突然出现的
He came out of nowhere.
就像是被鬼魂袭击了一样
It's like I was hit by a ghost.
鬼魂
By a ghost?
这不行  伙计  你得...
This is not right, man, you gotta...
你好  队长
Yo, captain!
你们不能直接  等一下  兰德里  等等
You can't just get... not now, Landry. Not now.
你们不能直接抢走我的案子
You can't just come and take my shit over.
怎么回事
What's going on?
武装抢劫  有数名人质
Armed robber, multiple hostages,
谈判专家无法联络劫匪
the negotiator can't make contact.
联邦储贷
我们为什么不进去
Why aren't we going in?
因为我们的案子刚刚变成了他们的
Pretty sure our scene just became theirs.
你们才来了十分钟
You weren't down here ten minutes ago.
这什么情况  我们怎么办
What is this? What do we do?
这样不对  我会记住的  我会记住的
This is wrong. I'm gonna remember that. I'm gonna remember that.
怎么回事
What's all that?
他们要我们退下
We've been asked to stand down.
我们现在只负责支援
We're here in support now only.
弗兰克  这太过分了
Frank, this is some bullshit, man.
要是我说了算
Like, if it was up to me...
兄弟
Hey, buddy.
歇一歇
Take a break.
警探
他们在哪
Where are they?
你背后
Behind you!
那些包  那些包  去追那些包
The bags! The bags! Follow the bags!
去追那些包
Get those bags!
银行小队出发
Bank units go.
所有人员封锁周边
All units set up a perimeter.
目标是男性  可能是白人
Subject is male, possibly Caucasian.
见鬼  我看不出
Shit, I can't tell.
当心
Watch out!
你还好吗
You all right?
别挡路  别挡路
Out of the way! Out of the way!
别挡路  走开  走开
Get out of the way! Go! Go!
-你还好吗  -嗯
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
新奥尔良警局  你听到没有
NOPD! You hear me?
拦住那辆车
Stop the car!
拦住那辆电车
Stop the streetcar!
有没有人看见一个隐...
Has anybody seen an invis...
拦住那辆电车
Stop the streetcar!
你被捕了
You're under arrest!
站住
Stop!
不准动  我能看见你
Freeze! I can see you!
新奥尔良警局  你被捕了
NOPD, you're under arrest!
我说了不准动
I said freeze!
不准动  别动
Freeze! Don't move.
弗兰克  当心
Frank! Watch out!
弗兰克  停  停
Frank, stop! Stop!
什么时候
老时间
[教堂]丘奇炸鸡
加一小份薯条
And a small fries.
从一到十级  十级最严重
Scale of one to ten, ten being the worst,
你现在有多疼
what's your pain right now?
-我不疼  -这里觉得疼痛吗
- It doesn't hurt. - Any soreness in here?
-不疼  -有没有失去意识
- No, ma'am. - Lose consciousness?
有片刻失去意识
For a second, I did there.
看我的手指  目光跟着它
Look at my finger. Follow it.
能让我们单独谈谈吗
Can you excuse us for a minute?
当然
Sure.
你今天是不是吃药了
Did you take a pill today?
是的
Yes.
把你的枪和警徽放到桌子上
Put your gun and the badge on the table.
警监
Captain.
枪和警徽  放到桌子上  快点
Gun and badge on the table, now.
如果我没吃  现在就死了
If I hadn't taken that, I'd be dead.
-你希望那样吗  -我希望我的警队遵守法律
- That what you want? - I want my police force to obey the law!
没有禁止这种药的法律
There are no laws on this drug!
明面上没有
They don't exist officially,
因为每次我们想处理
'cause every time we try to deal with it,
就会有穿西装的人来阻止我们
some guys in suits show up and tell us to stop.
我不知道今天来的那两个
Look, I don't know who those two were that came in today
制止你的人是谁
and cut you off at the knees.
我不知道他们是联调局还是军方
I don't know if they're feds or military or what,
但显然你完全受制于他们
but clearly, they have you under their thumb.
你肯定不痛快
And I don't think you like it.
因为他们不在乎这座城市的居民
'Cause they don't care about the people of this city.
不像你我这样在乎
Not like you do, not like I do,
而且我们都知道上一次
and we know what happened
我们指望穿西装的人
last time we were counting on guys in suits
保护新奥尔良的结果
to look out for New Orleans.
你要我来当坏人也没关系
Now, you need to make me the bad guy, that's fine.
但我猜你肯定知道不能说的情报
But I'd be willing to bet you know more than you're allowed to say.
也许我们可以私下合作查案
Maybe we can work together on this, unofficially.
也许我们能做点好事
And maybe we can do some good.
这不是我们的职责吗
And isn't that our job?
警监  正在转移嫌疑人
Captain, suspect is currently being removed from the premises.
新奥尔良警局
如果被人发现  别说是我给你的
Anybody finds you with that, you didn't get it from me.
我听说他是超能药的供货源
I'm told he's the source of Power.
我们把他拿下  就能救我们的城市
We shut him down, we get our city back.
他是谁
Who is he?
他是你的免罪金牌
He's your get-out-of-jail-free card.
斯莱德尔市有人徒步跑过了警车
目击者称不明人士的奔跑时速肯定超过了70公里
你还好吗  宝贝
You okay, honey?
-还要来点什么吗  -不用  我很好
- You need anything else? - No, I'm fine.
你确实养眼
Yes, you are.
你要来点什么吗
So, can I get you anything?
有热水吗
You got any hot water?
-我想喝热水  -好  我给你拿
- I'll take some of that. - Yeah. Okay, I'll get that for you.
杰西卡
Jessica!
给我倒杯热水好吗
Can I get some hot water?
纽特  你在里面吗
Newt, you in there?
纽特
Newt.
不是吧
Seriously?
你看见是谁干的了吗
Say, you saw who did this?
没有  我刚出来
No, I just came out the door.
妈妈
你买汤了吗
不要  不要  等等  放开我
Please! Please! Wait! Get off me!
救命
Help me!
我是罗宾  你知道该怎么做
It's Robin. You know what to do.
是我
Hey, it's me.
我需要补货  老地方见
I need to re-up, so meet me in the usual spot.
放我出去  拜托  放我出去
Let me out! Please, let me out!
你接着在里面踢啊
You keep kicking around in there.
我们先说好了
This how we gonna do this.
踢来踢去没有任何用
All that kicking ain't making no sense.
救命啊
Somebody help!
你在陌生的地方陌生人的车里
You in a strange man's car in an even stranger place.
救命
Help!
Help, please!
但我要和你谈谈
But I need to have a conversation with you.
我要直视
I need to be able to look...
我要直视你的眼睛
I need to be able to look you in your eye.
你要是不冷静下来
You don't wanna calm down,
我可能就得开车去一趟公园街32号
maybe I need to make a trip over to 32 Park, right?
你知道公园街32号在哪吗
You know where 32 Park is?
如果我放你出来  你开始大叫
Well, if I let you out and you start crying,
那我就要去拜访一下艾琳了
I'ma pay a little visit to Irene.
确保她没事
Make sure she all right, huh?
我看你很爱艾琳  因为你不闹了
I take it you love Irene 'cause you ain't knocking no more.
所以打开后备箱后
So when I open this up,
我们要好好谈谈
I want my conversation.
我们何不简单一点  从头开始
Why don't we start from the beginning, make it simple?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
我叫罗宾
I'm Robin!
我听不见你说话
Oh, I can't hear you.
-叫什么  -罗宾
- What is it? - Robin.
罗宾
Robin.
你卖超能药  是不是
You push that Power, don't you?
我不知道那是什么
I don't know nothing about that...
-你不知道  -不知道
- You don't know? - No! I don't!
或许你会想起来的
Maybe you'll figure it out, huh?
你在里面待到想起来为止吧
You stay in there until you figure it out.
我不知道
I don't know!
供货源在哪
What's the source?
-我不知道  -你不知道吗
- I don't know. - You don't know?
或许你知道纽特的事
Maybe you know something about Newt.
我不...我不知道
I don't... I don't know...
-你不知道纽特是谁  -不知道
- Oh, you don't know who Newt is? - No.
真有意思  你手机里都是纽特的信息
That's funny because Newt be all in your phone.
我总是收到奇怪的短信
I get weird texts from people
因为这份工作就是这样
all the time because that's what the job is.
那我跟你说说更奇怪的事
Well, let me tell you what's even more weird.
-纽特已经不在了  -什么
- Newt ain't here no more. - What?
既然纽特不在了  那我们要去哪
So since Newt ain't here, that leads us to... where to, huh?
去哪  罗宾  我要知道供货源在哪
Where to, Robin? I need to know where the source is.
我不...相信我
I don't... Believe me!
我叫你出来
I said get out!
为什么
Why?
这样你才能提升地位
So you can advance your position in life.
这是谁
Who is that?
-仔细看  是大佬吗  -我不知道
- Hmm? Look closer, is that Biggie? - I don't know.
-你不知道  -我不知道
- You don't know? - No, I don't know.
你混迹街头却什么都不知道
Oh, you on these streets, you don't know shit.
我知道你很害怕
I know you're scared.
我知道你在考虑反抗还是逃跑
I know you're feeling like fight or flight,
但我告诉你  你只能深呼吸挺过去
but I'ma tell you right now, you just breathe and get through it
因为你不知道我是谁  我要干什么
because listen, you don't know who I am and what I'm about,
但我必须找到供货源
but I got to find that source.
我得找到食物链最顶层的人物
I need to get to the top of the food chain.
但如果你继续跟我胡闹
But you keep messing around with me
装作你什么都不知道
and acting like you don't know shit,
我就先揍你一顿
I'm gonna knock your ass out,
然后杀了你妈妈
and then I'm gonna go kill your mother.
我要杀了艾琳
I'ma kill Irene.
看看我的眼睛
Look me in my eyes.
我在说谎吗
Am I lying?
告诉我你的决定
So tell me your decision.
我们的买家到了
There's our buyer.
你信任她吗
You trust her?
她和南美的所有贩毒集团都有联系
She's connected to every cartel in South America.
真正的大人物
She's the real deal.
钱呢
And the money?
你会拿到的
You'll get it.
我们的资助者会看清我们已经明白的事
Then our backers will see what the rest of us have already seen.
那是什么
What's that?
我们的女老板将改变世界
That we're working for the woman who's gonna change the world.
欢迎
Bienvenidos.
欢迎  我看你轻装前来
Welcome. I see you packed light.
我以为会有
I was expecting...
行李袋
duffel bags.
钱已经带来了
The money is here...
前提是产品名副其实
if the product lives up to its reputation.
产品
Product?
这不只是产品
It is not just a product.
这些药能颠覆政府
These pills will topple governments.
你即将成为南美最有权势的女人
You're about to become the most powerful woman in South America.
既然如此  我很期待你的展示
In that case, I look forward to your demonstration.
救命
我看见你在干什么了
Hey, I see what you doin'.
手机给我
Give me this.
照我说的做
You do what I told you.
别捣乱
No messing around.
接线员
Operator.
你好
Hi.
有人告诉我如果遇到麻烦就打这个电话
I was told to call this number if I ever had a problem.
去帕特森路尽头的香港超市
Go to Hong Kong Market off of Patterson.
走到后面说要鳄鱼酒
Go to the back and ask for alligator wine.
一个人来
Come alone.
好
Okay.
在里面无论你见到谁
You're gonna go meet whoever's in there,
都要按照我们说好的讲
you're gonna tell them what we talked about.
你告诉他们  你看到我了  然后我走了
You're gonna tell them that you saw me and that I left.
-不  -如果他们问
- No... - And if they ask...
不  你说给你指路  我指路了
No, you said point you in a direction, that's a direction.
你听说过矿井老鼠吗
You ever hear of a mine rat?
听起来像是会被炸死的老鼠
It sound like a rat that get blown up.
那就是你
Well, that's what you are.
你就是我的矿井老鼠
You're my mine rat.
我只是想维持生计  我还是个孩子
Look, I was just trying to make ends meet. I'm just a kid, I'm...
我知道在打什么主意
I know what you trying to do!
你在街头卖药  你他妈才不是孩子
You out here in these streets dealing, you ain't no damn kid.
你放弃了那条路
You gave that up.
别总是拿"我还是个孩子"当挡箭牌
You can't keep playing that whole "I'm just a child" card, okay?
办正事吧
Let's make it happen.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
食品超市
打扰一下
Excuse me.
鳄鱼酒
Alligator wine?
没这个东西
That's not a thing.
你能问问别人吗
Can you just ask somebody?
他说在这里等
He said wait here.
打扰一下  能帮我个忙吗
Excuse me, could you help me out with this?
什么
What?
-这个辣还是不辣  -我不知道这他妈是什么
- Is it spicy, is it mild? - I don't know what the fuck it is.
我不在这工作
I don't work here.
小心脚下
Watch your step.
先坐下吧
Okay, why don't you have a seat?
你从哪拿到的号码
How'd you get the number?
纽特给我的
Newt gave it to me.
你是个药贩
You're a dealer.
他给我这个号码  以防出现意外
Yeah, he gave it to me in case something went wrong.
纽特死了
Newt's dead.
我知道
I know.
怎么回事
How'd that happen?
有个人
There's this guy.
他自称"少校"
He calls himself "The Major".
他杀了纽特
He killed him.
然后把我扔进后备箱里
Then he threw me in his trunk.
他就在外面
He's right outside.
我能走了吗
Can I go?
你应该在这里待着
You should stay right here.
现在对你来说  这里是最安全的地方
This is the safest place for you right now.
你是大佬吗
You Biggie?
我不是大佬
I'm not Biggie.
大佬在销售部门  这是配送部门
Biggie works in sales. This is distribution.
-跟我说说  -我可以...
- Talk to me. - Listen, I can...
我不想和中间人谈  我已经谈过了
I don't want to talk to any middle men. Already did that.
你不告诉我大佬在哪
You don't tell me where Biggie is,
我就砍了你的头
I'll cut your fucking head off.
启动卡车
Start the truck!
让我出去
Let me out!
罗宾
Hey, Robin!
你还在里面吗
You still in there?
-你没事吧  -没事
- You all right? - Yeah. Yeah.
别担心  我来...
Don't worry, okay? I'm gonna come...
都没事了
Everything's okay.
特蕾西
Tracy.
宝贝
Baby.
见到你太好了
It's so good to see you.
什么
What? What?
捂住你的耳朵
Cover your ears.
那是什么
What's that?
他们在追踪超能药  每颗胶囊里都有芯片
They're logging Powers. There's chips in every capsule.
政府不让他们试验  他们就在我们身上试验
The government won't let them test it, so they test it on us.
你的买家
The people that you're selling to,
都是小白鼠
they're the lab rats.
那些是什么
What's all that?
10月14日  1小时45分钟后开始
今晚  展示
那是给潜在买家的展示
It's a demonstration for potential buyers.
意味着他们要离开新奥尔良了
It means they're done with New Orleans.
意味着我时间不多了
It means I'm running out of time.
我得去那
I gotta go there.
你得带我去那
You gotta take me there.
特蕾西  带...
Tracy, take...
救命
Help!
罗宾  我得...
Robin, I need...
拜托
Please.
你杀了我表哥
You killed my cousin.
他服药过量  我没杀他
He ODed. I didn't kill him.
我有钱
I got money.
求你了
Please.
我只是  我只是想找到我女儿
I'm just trying... I'm just trying to find my daughter.
番茄汤
冷静点
Yo, chill.
你得冷静下来
Yo, you need to calm down.
你晕过去了  我把你带到兽医院
You fell out, I brought you to the vet.
我妈在这工作
My mom work here.
这是你缝的
You did this?
是的
Yeah.
但我还没缝完射出伤口
But now I need to finish the exit wound.
你让不让我缝
You gonna let me do it or not?
我当你同意了
I guess that's a yes.
等一下
Wait, wait, wait.
怎么
What?
你给人缝合过吗
Y'all work on humans?
没
Nope.
我还没碰到你呢
I didn't even do nothing yet.
很多女孩长得像她
There a lot of girls that look just like her!
莱利夫人  你想让你的女儿丢掉性命吗
Mrs. Reilly, do you want your daughter to end up dead?
我跟你说了  我不知道她在哪
I already told you, I don't know where she is.
她几个小时前就该回家了
She was supposed to be home hours ago. What...
恕我直言  警官  很多女孩...
With all due respect, officer, there's a lot of girls...
你和你女儿可能都没有好下场
This could get very ugly for your daughter and for you.
你确定是她吗
Are you sure it was her?
你确定你没认错吗
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
你确定你没见过这个男人
Are you sure you haven't seen this man before?
没见过  我跟你说了  我不知道你在说什么
No, I told you I don't know what you talking about.
真有意思
That's funny.
我们的监控录像显示
We have surveillance footage
今晚你女儿和这名男子
of your daughter with this man tonight
在距此约八公里处实施了犯罪行为
committing crimes about five miles from here.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
场面可能会变得很难看
This could get a whole lot uglier for you.
亲爱的  家里没有那种小众洗发水了吗
Honey, bear. Are we all out of that one hippie shampoo that...
搞什么鬼  你们是谁
What the shit's going on here? Who the hell are you guys?
你怎么在我浴室里
What you doing in my bathroom?
-我们是警察  你是谁  -老兄  我住这
- We're the police. Who are you? - Man, I live here.
宝贝  抱歉用了你的浴室
Babe, I'm sorry I was in your shower.
你浴室的水压更强
It's just that the pressure's so much better in yours.
过来一下好吗
Can you come over here?
对不起  我只能这样
I'm really sorry. It had to happen that way.
罗宾派我来的
Robin sent me.
让我对付这些家伙吧
Let me just handle these guys, okay?
警官们
Officers.
你们刚说是哪个分局的来着
What precinct did you guys say you're from?
他们没说
They didn't say.
先生  此住址下登记的
Sir, Mrs. Reilly and her daughter
好像只有莱利夫人和她女儿两个人
seem to be the only residents registered to this address.
是吗
I see.
因为我不在你们的小数据库里  我就不能...
So now because I'm not in your little database, I can't...
百岁
Bless you.
房子里有猫吗
Is there a cat in here?
你不是说你住在这里吗
I thought you said you lived here.
没错  长官
Yes, I do, sir.
这很难以置信吗  怎么
Is that so hard to believe? Why?
就因为我是白人吗
Is it because I'm white?
你是觉得我和这位美丽的黑人女性
Are you assuming that me and this beautiful black woman
不可能组建一个幸福家庭吗
wouldn't be able to share a happy home?
你敢对着镜头说吗
You wanna say that on camera?
-宝贝  你手机呢  -给
- Babe, where's your phone? - Got it.
好的  让我们拭目以待
All right. Well, let's just see about this.
现场直播中
And we are live streaming.
让我把证据都录下来
Now, let's just get this on record.
宝贝  这两个人踏进家门时
Honey, did either of these men show you a warrant
向你出示搜查令了吗
when they came into our house?
没有
No, they did not.
那他们向你出示警徽了吗
And did either of them show you a badge?
没有  我能看看你们的警徽吗
No! Can I see your badges?
先生们
Gentlemen.
谢谢您的配合  莱利夫人
Thank you for your time, Mrs. Reilly.
不好意思  我认识你吗
I'm sorry, do I know you?
你有胶带吗
You got any duct tape?
胶带  要它干嘛
Duct tape? What?
住手  你到底是谁
Stop! Who are you?
我是新奥尔良警局的弗兰克·谢弗警探
My name is Detective Frank Shaver, NOPD.
我能看看你的警徽吗
Can I see your badge?
显然我没带在身上
Well, I don't have it on me.
那你放哪里了
Where do you have it?
莱利夫人  你女儿和我已经
Mrs. Reilly, your daughter and I have had a
共事了大半年了
professional friendship for a little over half a year now.
她是个聪明又心地善良的年轻人
She's a very smart and good-hearted young person,
可她惹上了一些不该惹的麻烦
but she is mixed up in some things she shouldn't be,
而我这是想要帮她
and I am trying to help her.
谢谢  这个我也得拿走
Thank you. I'm gonna need this too.
你自己的呢
Where's yours?
你的超能力是什么
So what's your power?
我不知道
I don't even know.
得了吧  你没吃过吗
Come on. You ain't tried it?
说实话
Honestly...
我见过一个服药过量致死的女孩
I saw a girl OD.
街头上他们都说
You know, on the streets,
那药能给你超能力
they're talking about how it'll give you superpowers,
但却不说只要一颗就可能致命
but not about how one hit could kill you.
是啊
Yeah.
要是你这么怕
Well, if you're so spooked,
为什么还要趟这浑水
why you still in the game?
老实在学校当个优等生不好吗
What happened to getting good grades and staying in school?
我倒是希望能当优等生
Yo, I wish I could get good grades.
去上学  考大学  再找份光鲜工作
Go to school, get to college, get some fancy-ass job.
但我现在就需要钱
But I need money now.
人人都缺钱
Everybody need money now.
我妈现在得了糖尿病
Well, my mother has diabetes now.
我们没有医保
And we don't got no health insurance.
她得做手术  手术费很贵
And she needs surgery, the expensive kind,
我还能怎么办
so what else am I supposed to do?
这还不简单
Oh, that's easy.
-什么  -去参军
- What? - Go to the army.
-怎么  杀人没对你产生影响吗  -当然有影响
- So what, it don't trip you up killing fools? - Yeah, it tripped me up.
但我就擅长这个
But that was my skill set.
而这个体制呢  它利用了我
And what did the system do? It took advantage of me.
不过我现在懂了  要想操纵体制
But I know now I got to work the system
就必须得比体制更高明
harder than it's working me.
你也一样
That's what you gotta do.
你年轻  是黑人  还是女性
You're young, you're Black, you're a woman.
这个体制注定会把你生吞活剥
The system is designed to swallow you whole.
你必须发现你比别人强的地方
You gotta find out what you do better than
并加以利用
anybody else and rock that.
你打算怎么办
So what you gonna do? Hmm?
你想做出什么事业
How you gonna leave your mark?
我会说唱
I rap.
算我错了  你的说唱艺名叫什么
I'm sorry. Well, what's your rap name then, huh?
你想干嘛  成为下一个卡迪·B吗
What you gonna be, the next Cardi B?
还是卡迪·C
Huh? Cardi C?
要不来两句
Well, go ahead and spit then.
既然你说你会说唱  那就让我听听
You say you rap, let me hear one line.
一句都唱不出来吗
You can't spit one line?
我不喜欢在别人面前唱
I don't like doing it in front of people.
害怕上台还怎么当说唱歌手
How you gonna to be a rapper if you got stage fright?
你知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
大多数情况下  人们不想做某件事
Most time, people don't wanna do something
是因为他们不行
is 'cause they're probably just wack at it.
你要是不行  直说就完了
If you wack, just say you wack.
好吧  给我个词
Fine, give me a word.
给你个词  什么意思
Give you a word? What you talking about?
我即兴说唱  给我个词
I'm gonna go off the top, give me a word.
你有这么厉害吗
Oh, you that good, huh?
猫科动物
Feline.
♪ 我马上就要腾空直上 ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to make a beeline ♪
♪ 将说唱界大小奖项都收入囊下 ♪
♪ And every single accolade for spitting 'bout to be mine ♪
♪ 我要从淘二手捡旧货换成设计款 ♪
♪ I'ma go from old shit and Goodwill to design ♪
♪ 我要像席琳·迪翁一样穿迪奥 ♪
♪ I'ma be rocking Dior like Dion, I'm Celine ♪
♪ 或许是思琳 ♪
♪ Or maybe I meant Céline ♪
♪ 我感觉十分清醒 ♪
♪ I'm feeling really cuh-lean ♪
♪ 谁去告诉那些大佬 ♪
♪ Can someone tell them other boys ♪
♪ 真正的说唱歌手要来了 绝不糊弄[蜂鸟]♪
♪ A real MC is coming, no humming ♪
♪ 我的名字选了另一种小鸟[知更鸟] ♪
♪ My name already chose a different bird ♪
♪ 这小小即兴根本不在话下  再给我个词 ♪
♪ I killed your little freestyle. Give me another word ♪
再给我个词
Give me another word.
地震仪
Seismograph.
♪ 这老兄想用地震仪把我干倒 ♪
♪ Dude trying to trip me up with his seismograph ♪
♪ 真是让我情不自禁想笑 ♪
♪ I think it's funny I can't pick a better time to laugh ♪
♪ 我会找到出路 ♪
♪ I'll find the path ♪
♪ 你不懂我的押韵实力有多强大 ♪
♪ You don't know all the rhymes I have ♪
♪ 我的大脑唯一玩不转的 ♪
♪ The only thing that don't sit well within this mind ♪
♪ 只有数学 ♪
♪ Is math ♪
抗生素
Antibiotic.
♪ 我大概需要抗精神病药  我就快疯了 ♪
♪ I might need an anti-psychotic, I'm going crazy ♪
♪ 新奥尔良逼我至此  可我还能掌控节奏 ♪
♪ NOLA made me and this flow, I got it ♪
♪ 就算大脑快要爆炸  我也全力以赴 ♪
♪ I been about it even if my mental space is crowded ♪
♪ 我把一切埋在心中  罪人才大声嚷嚷 ♪
♪ I keep it in because a guilty dog gonna bark the loudest ♪
♪ 我妈最为我骄傲  我们定能度过难关 ♪
♪ My mom's the proudest and I know that we can make it out if ♪
♪ 我们曾经历滔天骇浪 ♪
♪ We made it through a flood ♪
♪ 也定能扛过严酷旱灾 ♪
♪ I bet we gonna get through the drought ♪
♪ 我也许人小式微 ♪
♪ I may be little, but in these waters ♪
♪ 但不会溺死水中 ♪
♪ You won't catch me drowning ♪
♪ 终有一天我要肆意遨游在钞票之中 ♪
♪ One day I'll swim in all them dollar bills I'ma be counting ♪
败给你了
You smoked that.
好吧
All right.
你很厉害  真的很厉害
You're good, damn good.
这就是你的超能力
That's your power.
好好发挥这个能力
You take that, you leverage that,
用你的超能力  干翻整个体制
you use your power to take the system down.
好吧
All right.
这是什么
And what's this?
你得吃四颗
You gotta take four of them.
上面说是给狗吃的
This says for dogs.
是啊  你可是大人物[大型犬]
Yeah, well, you a big dog.
艾琳的手机
超级巨蛋体育场
你现在要去哪
Well, where you going now?
-记得照片里那个男人吗  -记得
- Remember that guy in the picture? - Yeah.
我得找到他
Gotta find him.
他抢走了我的东西  我得夺回来
He took something from me. I gotta get it back.
是东西还是人
Something or someone?
-我们还没完呢  -给我
- We ain't done here. - Give me...
别得寸进尺
Listen, don't press your luck.
我可以给你导航
I could navigate for you.
你不是要去屏幕上那个地方吗
You're going to where the dots on the screen is.
我能带你去
I can take you there.
只要一万块
For ten grand.
我为什么要平白无故地给你一万美元
Why the hell would I pay you $10,000 for anything?
医疗开销  保命费  绑架费
Medical expenses, keeping your ass alive, kidnapping fee.
钥匙给我
Give me those keys.
依我看  我给你优惠不少了
I'd say I done you a lot of solids here.
好吧
All right.
-两千  -五千
- Two. - Five.
这就是你女儿  特蕾西
So, this is your daughter, Tracy.
嗯
Yeah.
挺像你的
She look like you.
你认为是那个胡子男把她抓走了
And you think that guy with the beard took her?
你听说过特里奥斯吗
You ever hear of Teleios?
没有
No.
那是什么
What's that?
国防承包商
Defense contractor.
他们是当年破解了基因密码的人
They were the ones who cracked the codes back in the day.
他们抓了很多游骑兵
Grabbed a bunch of Rangers,
都关在一个屋子里  让他们暴露在辐射下
put 'em all in the room, filled them up with radiation.
乱改他们的基因
Messed with their genes.
想把我们变成超级英雄
Tried to turn us into superheroes.
他们为什么想制造超级英雄
Why'd they wanna make superheroes?
其实他们意不在此
They didn't. Not really.
因为在现实世界中  能力只有一个去处
'Cause in the real world, the power goes to where it always goes,
就是回到那些已掌握权力的人手中
to the people that already have it.
好吧  那你的超能力是什么
Okay. So, what's your power?
我知道你吃过药
I know you took it.
我吃过一次
I tried it once.
差点把我自己害死  还伤了很多人
Damn near killed me, hurt a lot of people.
所以我决定再也不吃那玩意了
So I said I'm not trying that shit no more.
几年后  特蕾西出生了
A few years later, Tracy came along.
我知道她不同于常人
I knew she was different though.
她小时候  从来不生病
When she was young, she never got sick or anything like that.
随着她长大  她变得越来越强壮
As she got older, she got stronger.
她表现出了一些
She exhibited symptoms of...
超能力的迹象
powers.
可她根本不需要吃药
But she never had to take a pill.
就像胎儿酒精综合症
Fetal alcohol syndrome.
如果你体内有很多垃圾
If you got, like, beaucoup shit in your system,
也许遗传给她了
maybe it got passed down to her.
好吧  虽然混迹街头  但也有点头脑
Oh, okay. Yeah, you hood, but you smart, huh?
总之  特里奥斯得知了特蕾西的存在
Anyway, when Teleios caught wind of Tracy,
就想故技重施  拿她做试验
they wanted to experiment on her like they did on me.
所以我们就跑了
And that's when we just took off.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
系上安全带
Put your seat belt on.
-我系上了啊  -你没系
- I got my seat belt on. - No, you don't.
系上安全带  听话
Put your seat belt on! All right?
有人在跟踪我们
Somebody's following us.
-没人跟踪我们  -坐稳了
- Nobody's following us. - Hold on.
-把头低下  -好好好
- Keep your head down. - Okay, okay, okay!
这个声音  照我说的做
This voice, do what I tell you to do, okay?
爸爸  小心
Daddy, watch out!
爸爸
Daddy!
特蕾西  不
Trace! No!
特蕾西
Tracy!
爸爸
Daddy!
爸爸  爸爸
Daddy! Daddy!
特蕾西
Tracy!
阿特
Art?
你还好吗
You okay?
加油  圣徒队
支票兑现
就是这里了
I mean, this is the spot.
就是这里
It's the spot.
就是那个人
So, there's that guy.
有什么计划
What's the plan now?
宝贝  快
Babe, come on.
-我来了  -快点  快点
- I'm coming. - Come on, come on.
有时候船到桥头自然直
You know what? Sometimes, the plan just walk right up on you.
明白我说的吗  我想要...
Know what I'm saying? That's what I'm trying...
抱歉  兄弟  你有火吗
Hey, man, I'm sorry, you got a light on you, man?
-小心点  -别  友善点
- Watch it. - No, be nice.
你非要这样吗
You gonna act like that, huh?
你的妹子让你挺爽吧  她长得不错
Your girl got you feeling good? She look good, man.
绑架费
Kidnapping fee.
你看到了什么
So what you see?
我看到了漂亮衣服
I see some fancy clothes.
趾高气昂的家伙
Stuck-up guy.
-趾高气昂的家伙拿着枪  -拿着枪
- Stuck-up guy with a gun. - With a gun.
他们绝对不是去兑现支票的  是吧
Man, they definitely ain't gonna cash no checks, you heard?
没错  绝对不是
No, not at all.
好  知道这些就够了
All right, that's all I need.
-怎么了  -你在干什么
- What? - What you doing?
我们不是蝙蝠侠和罗宾吗
I thought we was like Batman and Robin.
我们不是蝙蝠侠和罗宾  那是电影  这是现实生活
We ain't Batman and Robin, that's a movie, this is real life.
我身上还有你的血
Man, I got your blood on me.
-我们是一起的  -听着
- We doing this. - Listen.
你留在这里等我回来  好吗
You just hang here and wait till I get back, all right?
谢了
Thanks.
来这里真高兴
Man, glad to be in here.
我在名单上的
I'm on the list.
-我的天  你好吗  兄弟  -有事吗
- Oh, man! What's up, man? - Can I help you?
尼科
Nico!
-听着  -是我啊  你不是尼科吗
- Man, look. - It's me. Ain't you Nico?
我不是尼科  这是私人派对
I ain't no Nico, this a private party.
-不  -你来错地方了
- No. - You got the wrong spot, man.
不  我知道我来对地方了
No, I know I got the right spot.
你不在名单上
You're not on this list, man.
这是私人派对  你得离开
It's a private party. You got to roll out.
特里奥斯
对  我的名字就是这个
Yeah, that's my name right there.
欢迎来到超能计划
Welcome to Project Power.
过去几个月里  我们去了许多城市
Over the last months, we've been going from city to city
进行...可以说是临床试验吧
in a kind of a... let's call them clinical trials.
我们谨慎行事
Our footprint is small,
并且迅速转移  避免引来不必要的监管
and we move on quickly to avoid unwanted oversight.
我们的目标很简单
Our goal is simple.
人类的下一次进化
The next evolution of the human species.
这就需要你们了
That's where you come in.
在你们的资助下  特里奥斯可以成为
With your financing, Teleios could become
世界上最强大的公司
the most powerful company in the world.
而你们能得到什么好处
What's in it for you?
看名字就知道
It's in the headline.
超能力
Power.
终结不公正竞争的超能力
Power to level the playing field.
或者你们想的话  可以彻底消除竞争
Or, if you like, destroy it entirely.
可以创造混乱的超能力
Power to create chaos.
可以重塑现实的超能力
Power to renegotiate your reality.
未来你们连药都不用吃
One day, you won't even need a pill.
话说得漂亮
Pretty words.
再具体点
Be more specific.
好  先介绍一下我的朋友  小蜥蜴
Sure. Let me tell you about my friend the little lizard.
可以自愈  甚至可以重新长出断肢
A healer who can stitch himself up and even regrow what he lost.
手  脚  眼  还有复杂的身体结构
Hands, feet, eyes, unfathomably complex structures.
章鱼伪装自己  在海床上隐形
The octopus camouflages herself against the sea floor.
狼獾蛙弄断自己的骨头  当作武器
The wolverine frog breaks its own bones to use as weapons.
它们有夜视能力  可以让骨头脱臼
They see in the dark, they dislocate their bones.
可以把水转化成血浆
They turn water into plasma.
它们可以击打  扼颈  调节体温
They punch, they strangle, they thermoregulate.
进化给了动物们
Evolution has given animals
我们梦寐以求的数不胜数的能力
countless abilities we can only dream of.
这么多的能力  拜托
So much power, por favor.
所有的基因潜能都隐藏在我们的DNA中
All the genetic potential hidden in our DNA
等待着被释放
just waiting to be released.
有了你们的投资
With your investment,
未来一颗药就能永远有效
one day, a pill that lasts forever.
别再梦想了
Stop wishing.
开始行动吧
Start doing.
发现你的超能力
Find your power.
那死亡因素呢
And the death factor?
是的
Yes, well...
结果可能有个体差异
Results may vary.
但在我们研发出能完全控制的化合物之前
But as we work to a compound that we fully control,
可以用隔离舱
we have the tank.
弗兰克
Hey, Frank.
你来这里做什么
What you doing here?
找你啊  你妈妈担心死了
Looking for you. Your mom is worried sick.
-她还好吗  -是的  她还好
- Is she okay? - Yes, she's okay.
他在哪
Where's he?
我不知道
I don't know.
你别糊弄我
Listen, don't bullshit me right now.
-我没有  -你在保护他吗
- I'm not. - Are you protecting him?
-没有  -你为什么要保护...
- No. - Why are you protecting...
他是坏人
This is a bad guy.
他为什么是坏人  因为他干了坏事吗
Why is he a bad guy? Because he's done some bad things?
那你呢  你也干坏事
What about you? You do bad things too!
这话说得有些道理
That is almost a good point,
但我干的坏事...
but the bad things that I have done...
他只是在找他的女儿
He's just looking for his daughter.
他做的一切都是为了她
Everything he's doing, he's doing it for her.
-你觉得这是坏人吗  -他是这么跟你说的
- That sound like a bad guy to you? - That's what he told you?
我清楚是这样
That's what I know.
你想念你爸爸  我也很难过
Look, I'm sorry that you miss your dad,
-但这人在编故事  -你少来这套
- but he's telling you a story... - Don't do me like that...
他不是来找他女儿的  他是来开展业务的
He's not here looking for his daughter. He's setting up shop.
-你觉得他是超能药的供货源  -是的
- You think he's the source of Power? - Yes!
他不是  他想消灭这种药
Well, he's not. He's trying to stop it.
是吗
Uh-huh. Okay.
如果这是真的  虽然我不信
If that's true, and by the way, I don't think it is,
但如果是真的  那他应该帮助我
but if it is, then he should be helping me.
如果不是真的  那他就是在骗你  他很危险
If it's not true, then he's lying to you and he's dangerous
我得把他抓起来
and I need to bring him in.
不管怎样  你都应该告诉我他在哪
Either way, you should tell me where he is.
女士们先生们  这就是你们不远万里前来见证的时刻
Ladies, gentlemen, the moment you've traveled so far to see.
-我会怎么样  -别担心
- What's gonna happen to me? - Don't worry.
隔离舱内完全安全
This tank is completely safe.
中情局也有一个
They have one at the CIA.
扭一下来激活
Twist to activate.
对
Yes.
真令人激动  朋友们
How exciting, my friends.
你们将目睹一种非常罕见的超能力
You're about to witness a very rare power.
体温调节
Thermoregulation.
这种能力可能比较激烈
This one can get a bit intense.
过来我跟你说两句
Let me talk to you a sec.
我们让她保持舒适
Let's make sure she stays comfortable.
看吧
Voilà.
你是新来的吗
Are you new?
不  我来过
No, I've been here...
这名单上有不该来的人
There's people on this list I don't think should be here.
比如谁
Like who?
你觉得如何
Qué te parece?
很厉害
Espectáculo.
是的
Yeah.
就像《冰雪奇缘》一样
Just like Frozen.
这不算什么  还有更厉害的
Esto es nada. Hay mucho más.
更厉害的
Mucho más.
她很享受
She's having a great time.
橄榄汁马提尼
Dirty martini.
-你就是那个人  -接下来这么做
- You're him. - This is what's gonna happen.
你要向左迈出两步
You're gonna take two steps to the left.
别看他们  看我
Don't look at them, look at me.
你要走出电梯  我就在你后面
You're gonna walk out of that elevator, I'ma be right behind you.
拜托  我就要卖出十万颗药了
Please. I'm about to sell 100,000 pills.
-先让我完成这笔交易  -不  没时间了
- Let me finish this sale. - No, we ain't got time for that.
该死
Shit.
-趴下  -别靠近
- Get down! - Don't come closer.
照他说的做
Just do what he says.
叫他把枪放下  跟他说
Tell him put it down. Talk to him.
照他说的做
Just do what he says.
把你们的枪放下
Put your guns down.
否则我现在就让他脑袋开花
You don't, I'll make a mess of him right now.
随便你怎么对他  我们只要这些药
You can have him. We're just gonna take the pills.
行  把药拿走  我们自己解决
Fine, take the pills. We can work it out.
立刻把箱子放下
Put the case down now!
别  别靠近
Don't! Don't come any closer.
谁都不想死
Nobody wants to die.
把你们的枪放下
Put your guns down.
我们谈谈
Let's talk.
好吗
All right?
我们谈谈
Let's talk.
好  很好
Yeah. That's good.
不
No!
警告
连接丢失
放我出去  放我出去  放我出去
Get me out! Get me out! Get me out!
放我出去
Get me out!
Get me out of here!
救救我  拜托
Help me! Please!
她在哪  我女儿在哪
Where is she? Where's my daughter?
-我们谈谈吧  -好
- Now let's talk. - Yes.
你想要什么都行  药  钱  什么都行
Whatever you want. Pills, money, anything.
我才不要你的破药
I don't want no frickin' pills.
这是谁  我去哪找他们
Who is this, and where do I find them?
-我不知道  -你不知道
- I don't know. - You don't know?
-就...拜托  不需要这样  -不知道
- Just... please, no need for this... - Huh? No?
现在你肯定知道了吧
I bet you know now, huh?
创世纪号  创世纪号
Genesis. Genesis.
创世纪号是什么东西
What the hell is Genesis?
整个行动都在一艘叫创世纪号的船上进行
The whole operation's on a boat called the Genesis.
我女儿就在那吗
Is that where my daughter is?
她在船上吗  快说我女儿在哪
Is she on the boat? Tell me where my daughter is!
-新奥尔良警局  放下武器  -天啊
- NOPD, drop your weapon! - Oh. God!
-救救我  -闭嘴
- Help me! - Shut up.
-马上把枪放下  -我做不到  长官
- Put the gun down, now! - I can't do that, chief.
我不是在请求你
I am not asking!
好吧  放下枪  举起手  老大  你说了算
All right, gun down, hands up. Boss, you running everything.
-只是我这里有点小状况  -我不在乎
- Just know I got a little hitch right here. - I don't care!
我明白你不在乎  但我得在乎
I understand you don't care, but I gotta care.
我只是想告诉你我服从命令  好吧
I'm just letting you know I'm complying, okay?
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的一切都将被用来...
Anything you say can and will be used...
-等等  等等  -怎么了
- Wait. Wait, wait, wait! - What now?
罗宾
Robin!
罗宾让我告诉你几句话
Robin told me to tell you something.
她说每个瞬间都伴随着看不见的决定
She said every moment comes with invisible decisions.
她让我告诉你矿井老鼠  地震仪...
She told me to tell you about mine rats and seismographs...
太长了  总之是说决定的
Man it was long. It was about decisions,
但最后她说  "我在说谎吗"
but in the end she said, "Am I lying?"
-你来干什么  -我担心啊
- What the hell are you doing here? - I got worried.
该死  那就是大佬吗
Shit, is that Biggie?
走  走  走  快离开这里
Go, go, go! Get her out of here!
-你还好吗  -才不好
- You okay? - Hell, no.
天啊
Jesus.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
拜托  弗兰克  我们得帮他
Come on, Frank, we gotta help him.
你已经帮过他了
You already did help him.
你带他来这里  你没注意到吗
You brought him here. Are you not paying attention?
他在利用你
He's using you.
怎么  你没利用我吗
What, and you don't?
至少他没骗我
At least he's being honest about it.
拜托  阿特  把你跟我说的事告诉他吧
Come on. Art, tell him what you told me.
回家吧
Go home.
-别这样  你不能放弃  -我说了
- No, come on, please, you can't give up. - I said...
-回家吧  -你不能放弃
- go home. - You cannot give up!
我长得像你爸爸吗
Do I look like your daddy or something?
没事的  好吗
It's okay, all right?
弗兰克
Frank!
-到地下室去  -你得帮他
- Down in the basement! - You gotta help him.
如果你逮捕他  他就再也找不到女儿了
He'll never find his daughter if you arrest him.
好吧  你俩都是怂包
Well, you're both a bunch of cowards!
弗兰克
Frank!
这里是新奥尔良警局
You've reached the voicemail of Captain Craine
克雷恩警监的语音信箱  请留言
of the New Orleans Police Department. Please leave a mess...
警监  我抓到那家伙了
Captain, I got the guy.
马上带他回局里  请回电
I'm bringing him in. Call me back.
你犯了个大错
You're making a big mistake.
让我猜猜  你是个好毒贩  是吗
Uh-huh. Let me guess, you're one of the good drug dealers, right?
你要拯救世界
You're trying to save the world.
他们抓了我女儿
They have my daughter.
这就是我的世界
That is my world.
听着  你现在离开还不晚
Listen, it ain't too late for you to walk away.
我说不好  哥们
I don't know, man.
你是戴着手铐的那个
You're the one in handcuffs,
而我才是开车的那个
and I'm literally in the driver's seat,
我搞错什么了吗
so what am I missing?
你搞错的是
What you're missing is
三十秒后  你的警监会打电话给你
in the next 30 seconds, your captain is gonna call you
让你把我带去别的地方  而不是你们分局
and tell you to take me to a different place, not the precinct.
但我们永远到不了那个地方
But we're never gonna make it to that place.
是吗  为什么
Oh yeah? Why is that?
想想你的所见所闻
Think about what you've seen.
在新奥尔良做试验
Testing in New Orleans.
为什么
Why?
地方当局被收买了
Local authorities on payroll.
为什么
Why?
而你的警监只派了一个警察
And then your captain sends out a single cop
去抓捕城里最危险的人  为什么
to apprehend the most dangerous man in the city. Why?
已抓到嫌犯
马上带他回来
不用了  待在原地别动
你们现在在哪
因为他要听从别人的命令
Because he's taking orders from someone else.
而且我还可以告诉你那边那辆车
And I can also tell you that that van over there...
不是送报纸的
ain't delivering newspapers.
我告诉你会发生什么
This what's gonna happen.
他们会杀了你  然后把我带走
They gonna kill you, and then they gonna take me.
我不介意他们把我带走
Now, I'm okay with that second part of this
只要能让我快点找到女儿
if it gets me to my daughter sooner.
-他们在这里做什么  -做实地测试
- What are they doing here? - Doing field testing.
如果他们能稳定药效  就会大规模生产
If they can stabilize it, then they'll mass produce it.
这里发生的事将会随处可见
So whatever's happening here is gonna start happening everywhere.
还有呢  你女儿跟这事有关系吗
And what? Your kid has something to do with it?
你觉得他们的配方是从哪里来的
Where do you think they got the formula from?
你需要什么
What do you need?
这事跟你无关
This ain't your fight.
这是我的城市
It's my city.
他们以为可以随意在新奥尔良人身上试药
They think they can just test their shit on the people of New Orleans
没人会在乎  没人会为此抗争吗
and no one's gonna care, no one's gonna fight them on it?
好  让他们看看会有什么后果  你需要什么
Well, let 'em see what happens. What do you need?
你身上还有药吗
You still got them pills on you?
那个警察呢
What happened to the cop?
把少校带到A层甲板
Get the Major to A deck.
所有人员和货物尽快上船
I want all personnel and cargo loaded ASAP.
创世纪号今晚出发
The Genesis leaves tonight.
你来这里干什么  我告诉过你...
What the hell are you doing here? I told you...
你吓死我了  我差点心脏病发作
You scared me half to death, almost gave me a heart attack!
-那些人有枪  -别对我大吼大叫发号施令
- Those men have guns... - Don't be barking orders at me...
-你不是我爸爸  -我们不是在商量
- You not my daddy... - We're not having this conversation.
过来
Come here.
-他们抓到阿特了  -对  我知道
- They got Art. - Yeah, I know.
你就让他们把他抓走吗
So you let 'em take him?
不  这是他计划好的
No, it was his plan.
这是他找到女儿的唯一方法
It's the only way he can get to his daughter.
我要在他后面闯进去
Now I gotta bust in after him.
那我们要怎么办
So what are we gonna do about it?
好  你想帮忙吗
All right, you wanna help?
你待在这里
You stay here.
把这个塞进耳朵里
Put this in your ear
然后告诉我有什么动静
and you tell me about what's coming and what's going.
拿着
Take it.
你是望风的
You're the lookout.
这个角色很重要
It's an important role.
测试  测试  测试
Testing, testing, testing.
我听到了
I hear you.
有几个持枪警卫就在你前面
You got a few guards with guns right in front of you.
好  谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
你应该模仿克林特·伊斯特伍德
I think you should do the Clint Eastwood thing.
我才不模仿克林特·伊斯特伍德
I'm not doing the Clint Eastwood thing.
还好吗
How's it going?
-我在楼上有个会  -站着别动
- I got a meeting upstairs. - Stay right there.
好
Okay.
你知道我是谁吧  新奥尔良港务局
You know who I am, right? NOLA dock authority.
你知道我不在乎吧
You know I don't care, right?
你听说过港务局长吗  那是我上司
You heard of a harbor master, right? That's my boss.
如果你上司不给我上司一万美元
Now, if your boss doesn't give my boss ten thousand dollars,
这艘船就哪都别想去
this vessel's not going anywhere.
我猜这艘船哪都不去了
I guess that vessel's not going anywhere.
他不买账  弗兰克
He's not down, Frank.
也许你可以模仿克林特·伊斯特伍德
I think maybe you gotta go with the Clint Eastwood thing.
快
Do it.
快  就像你对着镜子练习一样
Come on, like you practiced in the mirror.
出自克林特·伊斯特伍德主演的
1971年电影《肮脏的哈里》
好吧  我想你只要问自己一个问题
Well, I guess you just gotta ask yourself one question.
我是要做出错误的决定
Am I gonna be the guy that makes a bad decision
让中间人空手而归
to send the bag man home empty-handed,
让老板从床上爬起来
make the boss get out of bed,
狠狠地修理犯错的人
start raining hellfire on whoever's responsible?
还是要做出正确的决定
Or am I gonna be the guy who makes a good decision
不要在这里挡路
and get the hell out of the goddamn way,
好让我们都能回家看圣徒队比赛集锦呢
so we can all get home in time to watch the Saints highlights?
棒  弗兰克
Yeah, Frank!
你要怎么办
So what's it gonna be...
废物
punk?
我是废物吗
I'm the punk?
我结巴了吗
Oh, did I stutter?
在这等着
Wait here.
我说了吧
I told you.
模仿得不错吧
Pretty good, right?
特蕾西在哪
Where's Tracy?
我是来找特蕾西的
I'm just here for Tracy.
她很安全
She's safe.
跟我来
Come with me.
我有答复给你
Hey, I got an answer for you.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
我们把他拖走
Let's get him outta here.
我知道你觉得我们做的事是错的
I know you think what we're doing here is wrong,
但你听说过海里埃塔·拉克丝这个人吗
but do you know the name Henrietta Lacks?
海里埃塔·拉克丝于1951年住院
Henrietta Lacks checks into a hospital in 1951
为了切除子宫颈肿瘤
to have a tumor removed from her cervix,
但医生在手术中不仅切除了肿瘤
but the doctor doesn't just take the tumor,
还采集了健康的细胞
he also takes healthy cells in the process.
弗兰克  等等  能听到我说话吗
Frank. Wait, can you hear me?
弗兰克
Frank?
你好啊
Hello there.
那些未经许可被偷走的细胞
Those cells, stolen without her consent,
是上世纪几乎所有
are the backbone of nearly every medical advancement
医学进步的基础
in the last century.
这一切都是因为有人看了那个女人一眼
All because someone took one look at that woman
看到了她真正的潜力
and saw her true potential.
特蕾西的试验结果太惊人了
Tracy's lab results are fascinating.
我们说的是永不消失的超能力
We're talking about permanent power,
人类进化的下一步
the next step in human evolution.
人类的伟大进步都是从黑暗中开始的  少校
All of our greatest advancements began in darkness, Major.
由先驱们照亮前路
It's up to the pioneers to light the way.
问题就在这里  博士
Well, you see, that's the thing, Doc.
你不是先驱
You not a pioneer.
你是毒贩子
You a drug dealer.
你还是把科研项目
How about you take your science project
塞进你老妈的...
and you shove it up your mother...
抓住他  带走
Grab him. Get him out.
带他下去
Take him below.
尽量收集他的遗传基因  剩下的冲走
Salvage whatever genetic material you can and flush the rest.
弗兰克
Frank.
不  你应该在望风的
No, you're supposed to be the lookout.
你中枪了
Well, you got shot.
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
怎么  你刀枪不入吗
So what, you bulletproof?
很酷吧
It's cool, right?
A5呼叫控制室
Alpha 5 to ops.
打开26号舱门
Open hatch 26.
该死
Shit.
-门  -控制室  26号舱门
- Doors. - Ops, hatch 26.
门
The doors.
26号舱门
Hatch 26...
干得漂亮
Nicely done.
他们要带他去甲板下面
They're taking him below deck.
甲板下二层
Sub level two.
好  看这里
Okay, so see here?
门禁控制
上层甲板
下层船体
所有关卡都有安全门
All the checkpoints got their own security doors.
如果我按下这两个按钮
And if I press those two buttons,
紧急封锁控制
整艘船都会进入封锁模式
the whole thing go on lockdown mode.
嗯  就像《廊桥遗梦》里一样
Yeah, that's like County.
你是说你可以帮我控制这些门
So you're saying you can open and close doors for me.
我觉得可以
I mean, I think so.
-怎么了  -待在这里
- Why? - Stay here.
-你要去哪  -我去找阿特
- Where you going? - I'm going after Art.
你要是遇到麻烦  就马上跑
You get in any trouble, you run.
你去船头等我
You meet me at the front of the ship.
如果可以  我会去那里
If I can get there, I will.
如果我去不了  你就继续跑
If I can't, then you keep running.
但是外面有数不清的警卫
But there's like a thousand guards out there.
但你知道我很厉害吧
But you know I'm awesome, right?
那就大显身手吧
Well, go be awesome then.
马上要开始吵了
It's about to get real noisy.
走错路了
Hey. Wrong way.
我知道
I know!
给我接华莱士
Get me Wallace.
少校控制住了吗
Is the Major secure?
正看着他呢
Got eyes on him right now.
去控制室  看看为什么警报响了
Get to ops, find out why this alarm is going off.
马上去
On it.
能听到吗  罗宾
Can you hear me, Robin?
能听到也能看到
Hearing and... seeing.
18号舱门
Hatch 18.
非常感谢
Merci "buckets."
有我呢
I got you.
好  现在我该往哪里走
All right, where am I going now?
另一头还有扇门
There's another door at the other end,
往左走  下楼
to the left, down the stairs.
A1呼叫控制室
Alpha 1 to ops.
打开15号舱门
Pop hatch 15.
A1呼叫控制室
Alpha 1 to ops.
15号舱门  快打开
Hatch 15, open it up.
弗兰克  我们有麻烦了
Frank, we got a problem.
快点
Let's go.
-那个大块头朝这边来了  -哪边
- That big dude's coming this way. - Which way?
我这边
My way.
你要多久才能启航
How quickly can you get us out of here?
大概需要十五分钟才能离港
About 15 minutes until we can release from the dock, ma'am.
给你十分钟
You got ten.
快点
Let's go!
-你快到了  -这边下去
- You're almost there. - Down here?
-下楼梯  右边最后一扇门  -收到
- Down the stairs, last door to the right. - Copy that.
去甲板下二层
Heading down to sub level two.
弗兰克  我好像找到她了
Frank, I think I found her.
我听不清  罗宾
Can't hear you, Robin.
弗兰克  我知道她在哪
Frank, I know where she is.
声音断断续续  你说你找到什么了
You're breaking up. What'd you say you found?
-什么  -特蕾西
- Something what? - Tracy.
-你说什么  -听到了吗
- What you say? - You hearing me?
罗宾  我没信号了
Robin, I'm losing you.
我听不清  罗宾
I can't hear you, Robin.
安保区  引擎区
Security deck, engine deck...
试验区
Lab deck.
-你说什么  你找到什么了  -能听到吗
- What did you say? You found what? - Can you hear me?
弗兰克  当心  你背后有人
Frank, look out, there's someone behind you!
什么鬼
What the...
弗兰克  门
Frank, the door!
把他弄到门那边  弗兰克
Just get him to the door, Frank.
都听到了吧
Y'all hear that?
那声音来自
That's the sound
世界上最先进的战术团队
of the most advanced tactical team in the world
他们要拿下这艘船
taking over your ship.
弗兰克  打他的蛋蛋
Frank, punch him in the nuts or something.
加油  弗兰克  你该发威了
Come on, Frank. It's time to be awesome.
准备关门
Get ready with the door!
关门
Close it!
操
Fuck!
华莱士  下面到底怎么回事
Wallace, what the hell is going on down there?
出口
汇报最新情况
Give me an update.
控制室没人
Room's empty.
她从逃生口跑了
She took the escape hatch.
不知跑哪去了
She could be anywhere.
你回少校那边去
You get back to the Major.
我们要了结这事
We are ending this.
把那小鬼给我找出来
Somebody find that kid.
我们得行动了
We gotta move.
交给你了
You got this?
你  跟我来
You. With me.
船已就绪
The ship is ready.
那就赶紧出海
Well, then get us out to sea.
创世纪号
我问你件事  大块头
Let me ask you something, big man.
世界上最强大的动物是什么
What's the most powerful animal on the planet?
闭嘴
Shut up.
有些人认为是狮子  因为它们体型大
Some people think it's the lion 'cause, you know, they big,
但实际上最强大的
but it's actually the...
是枪虾
the pistol shrimp.
个头很小  看起来人畜无害
Little bitty guy, look harmless,
但它攻击速度超快  能让周围的水蒸发
but hit you so fast, it vaporizes the water around it.
比太阳表面的温度还高八千度
Eight thousand degrees hotter than the surface of the sun.
造成的冲击波
The shock waves,
让猎物骨肉分离
rips the flesh right off the bone.
尘埃落定后
And when it's all over,
就剩虾先生坐在那里  嘴里啃着
it's just Mr. Shrimp sitting there, eating...
剩下的残躯
anything that's left.
所以呢
Yeah, so?
所以
So...
我们的这些能力都来自于动物  对吧
We get all these powers from animals, right?
猜猜我的是哪种动物
Guess what animal I got?
你做出了正确的选择
You made the right choice.
聪明人
Smart man.
你在搞什么
What the hell are you doing?
滚出来
Get the fuck out of here!
老实讲
Gotta be honest,
没动手就把你抓住了我有点失望
I was a little disappointed we took you without a fight.
很多朋友因为你丢了性命
Got a lot of dead friends because of you.
特里奥斯
动手吧
Let's go.
你笑什么
Something funny?
不准动
Don't move!
你可真够慢的
Took you long enough.
是啊  不用客气
Yeah, you're welcome.
另外  那可真恶心  走吧
That's disgusting, by the way. Come on.
特蕾西
Tracy?
我是罗宾
I'm Robin.
我得带你离开这里
I gotta get you out of here.
我跟你爸爸一起来的
I'm with your dad.
我得带你回他身边
I gotta bring you to him.
他在这船上
He's here.
真的吗
Really?
他来了
He came?
我就知道他会来
I knew he'd come.
好了  我去检查另一个房间
All right, I'm gonna check the other room.
不
No!
你立刻去甲板上
I want you on the deck now.
-她只能从那里下船  -遵命
- It's the only way she can get off this damn ship. - Yes, ma'am.
全体安保人员保持高度警惕
All security personnel should be on full alert.
试验对象失踪  多人入侵
The asset is missing. Multiple intruders.
我要彻底搜查这艘船
I want a full sweep of the ship.
我们不能停下
We gotta keep moving.
那是罗宾的声音吗
Was that Robin I heard?
是  她在控制室
Yeah, she's in the control room.
她知道特蕾西在哪
I think she knows where Tracy is.
16号舱门
Hatch 16.
罗宾  16号舱门
Robin, hatch 16.
好吧  我们得去船头了
All right, we gotta get to the bow.
-特蕾西  -罗宾
- Tracy? - Robin?
她在哪  特蕾西
Where is she? Tracy?
什么情况
What's going on?
我告诉她有麻烦就到船头碰面
I told her anything goes wrong, meet at the front of the boat.
特蕾西
Tracy.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
阿特
Art.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
你没事吧
You okay?
我带你离开  来吧
Let's get you out of here. Come on.
我们还剩多少时间
How much time we got left?
不到五分钟  大于零分钟
Less than five, more than zero.
-你的药还没吃  -嗯  我留着呢
- Still got your pill? - Yeah, I'm saving that one.
留着做什么
Saving it for what?
最后一招
Last resort.
交给我  快走
I got this, go!
带她上救生艇
Get her to the lifeboat!
快点
Come on!
罗宾呢
Where's Robin?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们得跑起来了  准备好了吗
All right, we're gonna run. Ready?
跟着我  走  走  走
Stay with me. Go, go, go!
快点  你爸爸马上就来
Come on! Your dad's right behind us.
别朝那女孩开枪
Don't shoot the girl!
卡住了
It's stuck!
-动手  -动手
- Now! - Now!
太好了
Yes!
去救生艇上等我
Meet me at the lifeboat.
-罗宾在哪  -我以为她跟你在一起
- Where's Robin? - Thought she was with you.
少校
Major!
停手吧  少校
Stop, Major!
看看我抓到谁了
You see who I have here?
放开我
Get off of me!
立刻让特蕾西出来
I want Tracy out here now!
-药给我  -你吃没用
- Give me the pill. - It's not gonna work on you.
-必须得我吃  -不  爸爸
- It's got to be me. - No, Daddy.
你知道会有什么后果
You know what'll happen if you do that.
否则我杀了她  阿瑟
I will kill her, Arthur,
就在你眼前杀了她
right now, right in front of you.
我爱你胜过世上的一切  你听到了吗
I love you more than anything in the world, you hear me?
我爱你  但是我们不能丢下她不管
I love you, but there's no way we're leaving her behind.
你们全部都下船  快点
All of you out of the boat, now!
要是出了什么差错
Look, if anything goes wrong,
你就放下救生艇逃走  好吗
you drop this boat down and get out of here, okay?
好的
All right.
我要了结这一切
I'm gonna end this.
别开枪
Hold your fire.
立刻让特蕾西出来
I want Tracy out here now!
等等
Wait.
-罗宾  你没事吧  -别跟她说话
- Robin, you all right? - Don't talk to her!
听我说  罗宾
Let me tell you something, Robin.
你做得非常棒
You did a great job.
你救了我女儿的命
You saved my daughter's life.
你听好  博士
Now you listen up, Doc!
你只有一次机会
You got one chance.
你放她走  我留你一命
You let her go, I let you live.
这不是谈判
This isn't a negotiation.
没错
No.
这不是谈判
It's something else.
我跟你说过会发生什么  不是吗
I told you what was gonna happen, didn't I?
你来告诉我
Now you tell me...
我在说谎吗
am I lying?
杀了他
Kill him!
醒醒  爸爸
Hey, come on Daddy.
爸爸  醒醒
Daddy, come on!
爸爸
Daddy!
爸爸  醒醒
Daddy, come on!
爸爸
Daddy?
太好了
Yes! Yes!
谢谢你
Thank you.
起来
Stand up.
都坐好了吗
Y'all ready?
特蕾西  你能治愈枪伤吗
Tracy, do you think you could heal a gunshot wound?
早上好  新奥尔良
Good morning, New Orleans!
谁说要打败圣徒队来着
Who dat say they gon' beat dem Saints?
昨晚巨蛋的比赛可真精彩啊
Man, it went down in the Dome last night.
但街上的动静更大
It was even louder on the streets.
你们听到昨晚比赛后
Did y'all hear about the
发生的两次爆炸了吗
two explosions last night after the game?
海岸警卫队说找不到出事船只
The Coast Guard's saying they can't find any sign of the ship,
新奥尔良警局也是三缄其口
and then, NOPD has absolutely nothing to say about it.
你接下来什么打算
So what's next for you?
首先我得跟警监好好谈谈
Well, first I think I'll have a long talk with my captain
然后也许找个想挖大新闻的记者
then maybe find a journalist looking for their next big story.
你要做吹哨人  就没有回头路了
You blow that whistle, ain't no going back.
是啊
Yeah.
等大家得知真相后
Well, let's see these assholes try to hide
看这帮混蛋还怎么隐瞒
when everyone knows what they're doing.
我问你个问题
Let me ask you something.
你觉得这事真的结束了吗
You think this is really over?
对我来说是的
For me, it is.
我们该走了
It's time to jet.
你
Hey, you.
去找我的车
Go to my truck.
好好检查后备箱
Make sure you check the trunk.
记得我说的吧
You remember what I said?
你很有天赋  罗宾
There's something great inside you, Robin.
好好利用
Use it.
拿着
Here.
-这是什么  -看起来像什么
- What's this? - What's it look like?
弗兰克
Frank.
我妈妈的手机怎么在你手上
Why you got my mama's phone, man?
说来话长
It's a long story.
我认真的
Seriously.
弗兰克
Frank!
番茄汤
我爱你  妈
I love you, Ma.
我也爱你
I love you too.
接下来这首歌绝对能震撼你们的心弦
Man, I am about to beat on your eardrums with this one.
这是新人说唱歌手
It's the first single
罗宾·莱利的首支单曲  合作歌手奇卡
from brand new MC Robin Reilly, featuring Chika.
走起
Let's go!
超能计划